I'm going to show you how to make a shot called a Sicilian Kiss, this is a really, really, really tasty shot.
And this is a great shot if you arrive late to the bar and you're trying to catch up with everyone else, so do it as a beer chaser, do your shot first, then chase it with a beer.
Alright, let me show you how to make this wonderful shot.
We're going to start off with an ounce of amaretto, you can also do a 1/2 ounce if you would like, but you're late, so you really, really need to catch up, so we're going to give you an ounce of amaretto, and an ounce of southern comfort.
Now I am using what's called a jigger to measure the alcohol for this shot.
These are really great, you can get them at a bar supply store, or a liquor store.
This side is an ounce, this side is a half ounce, perfect for parties, use it at work, great for mixing your drinks so you get your proportions correct.
Alright.
Now you have here what is called a Sicilian Kiss.
Like I said, chase it with a beer, or you can pour this over ice, and you can do it as a chill shot, and either way, it's going to be really tasty.
Enjoy.